Privacy Policy for turtlegames.org
==================================

At Turtle Games, accessible from turtlegames.org, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Turtle Games and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Turtle Games. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

Consent
-------

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

Log Files
---------

Turtle Games follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

Cookies and Web Beacons
-----------------------

Like any other website, Turtle Games uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' darkmode preferences. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on if you click the darkmode button or not.

Children's Information
----------------------

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Turtle Games does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
